#### Hello.

#### My name is John Damits

I have a passion for using code and digital design in non-traditional ways, especially by combining the creative aspects of Computer Science with my Asian Studies experience in order to foster inter-cultural understanding.

Tel: (724) 209-8709 Mail: hello@idamits.com https://jdamits.com Portfolio:

# **Experience**

**Atlantic Nitrogen & Testing** | Engineer, Job Site Supervisor 5.2013 - Present

• In charge of software development process involving pipeline integrity testing

• Designed and built websites and data server for the company

1.2017 - 8.2018 **Link2Launch** | Software Engineer

• Worked with principals to develop ideas and technologies for their business

6.2016 - 8.2016 **Knox College CS Department** | Research Internship

• Worked with Java, HTML, CSS, and Javascript to create teaching tool and website

6.2015 - 8.2015 **Zego Robotics** | Software Engineer, Designer

• Designed and built robots for a robotics company in Pittsburgh

• 3D modeled and build a prototype human assistance robot

# 02. Education



**Knox College** | Bachelor of Arts Computer Science + Asian Studies KNOX GPA: **3.91** | Summa Cum Laude | 2017



Case Western Reserve University **Computer Science** 

GPA: **3.03** | 2013 to 2015

### Skills and Accomplishments

English | Japanese | Java | C/C++ | Python | HTML | CSS | Javascript Languages

Coursework **Software Development** | Worked in an *AGILE* team

> **Parallel Programming** | Parallelization of large cluster systems **Cognition and Design** | Approaches to design and programming

**Senior Patrol Leader** | Troop 58 **Eagle Scout** 

**Japanese Club President** | Organized weekly meetings, I-Fair, and club trips

**National Honors Society** Phi Beta Kappa Smash Bros. Club **Founder and President** 

**Professor Amy Absher** | CWRU | Published in a book SAGES program **Research Assistant** 

**Professor Jaime Spacco** | Knox College | Teaching intro CS courses